Now, let's take a look at some numeric variables in this data set.
现在 让我们来看一下这个数据集里的数值变量
Let's start this example by looking at Pokemon speed.
比如宝可梦的速度
The higher the value, the sooner they will act in battle.
速度值越高 宝可梦出招越快
Matplotlib has a built in function for creating histograms, the Hist Function.
Matplotlib 有一个内置函数可创建直方图 即 hist 函数
We can create the basic histogram in the same way as the bar chart.
创建基础直方图的操作与创建条形图相同
Data set to the Pokemon data frame and X to the speed variable.
将参数 data 设为 pokemon 数据集 参数 x 设为 speed 变量
The distribution of speed values appears uni-modal and slightly right skewed,
速度值看起来是单峰分布 而且稍向右偏
but there isn't a lot of detail here.
但可以研究的细节并不多
By default, matplotlib will split the data into 10 bins,
这是因为 matplotlib 默认把数据分为十组
which is usually too few.
而这个组数通常都太少
In addition, the bin boundaries are not particularly aligned
另外 数据的组边界和坐标轴刻度也没怎么对齐
with the tick marks making interpretation trickier.
这不利于解读数据
To solve this, we want to use the bin's parameter of the Hist Function.
我们可以用函数 hist 里的参数 bins 来解决这个问题
If we set an integer value for the bins,
如果给 bins 设一个整数值
such as 20, then that will set the number of bins that will be used for plotting.
比如 20 那绘制出来的图表就包含 20 个 分组 (bin)
We have a more detailed look at the data,
现在数据细节清晰多了
but this still has the problem of awkward bin boundaries.
但组边界还是模糊不清
You can see the bin edges and counts return by hist when I remove the semicolon.
如果我去掉分号 你就可以看到函数 hist 返回的组边界和分组数量了
The fact that bin edges are non integer and the data values are integer,
组边界非整数 而数据的值为整数
will mean that some bins cover more integer values than others.
导致有些组包含了比较多的整数值
Instead, a better way of making use of the bins
因此 我们应该用参数 bins
parameter is to specify the bin boundaries explicitly.
来指定组边界
Here, I'll make use of Numpy's arange function to create bins of size five.
这里我用 Numpy 的函数 arange 创建了组距为 5 的分组
The first argument is the minimum value,
第一个参数为最小值
while the second argument,
第二个参数
will be the maximum value.
为最大值
The third argument gives the step-size for the bins.
第三个参数是组距
One thing that I will do here is to add plus five to the second argument.
这里我给第二个参数加了 5
This is because the values generated by arange will not include the maximum value.
这是因为 arange 生成的值不包括最大值
Only those things strictly lower than the max.
一定会是低于最大值的值
By adding plus five,
加了 5
this means that all values should be represented in the chart.
所有值就都能呈现在直方图中了
When I add the bins list to the Hist Function,
将列表 bins 传入到函数 hist 里
this creates a view of the data that implies the data is approximately uni-modal,
就会生成一个图表 可以观察到数据大致上符合单峰分布
save for a bit of a dip in the 75-85 range.
除了 75-85 区间那里有些凹陷
What happens if we try an extremely small bin size? Like one?
如果我们把组距设得极小 会怎么样呢？比如 1
On the one hand, this bin size is perhaps a bit too small,
一方面 这个组距或许太小了
introducing a lot of noise in the plot.
图表中多了很多噪声
On the other hand, this does a good job of showing that
另一方面 这又很好地体现了一点
Pokemon's speed statistics are usually divisible by five.
宝可梦的速度统计数据通常可以被 5 整除
Seaborn also has a function for creating histograms, Distplot.
Seaborn 也有一个函数可以创建直方图 即 distplot
Unlike the countplot and Hist function seen before,
与之前的函数 countplot 和 hist 不同
the main argument taken by the function is just the panda series containing all the data.
函数 distplot 的主要参数只是包含所有数据的 pandas Series
You'll notice two things about this plot.
不难发现这个图表有两个特点
First of all, the default bin count is larger than in matplotlib.
第一 默认组数比 matplotlib 的多
Secondly, you'll notice that a line has been plotted over
第二 你会发现条形上有一条线
the bars and that the Y axis values are very small.
而且 y 轴的值很小
This is because the line is a density curve estimate of the data distribution,
这是因为这条线代表的是概率分布的估计曲线
and the total area underneath the curve is set to be =1.
曲线下方的总面积为 1
If you're interested in this kind of plot,
如果你对这类图表感兴趣
you can read up more about this in the extras at the end of this lesson.
可以在课程结尾部分 查看补充内容
You can turn off the density curve by setting the parameter kde=false.
要关闭密度曲线 只需将参数 kde 设为 False 即可
With this parameter, you can see that
用了这个参数
the histogram is plotted alone with counts on the Y axis.
直方图就只有 y 轴的数量统计 没有密度曲线了
However, since we're back to the basic histogram,
不过既然我们又回到了基础直方图
we might as well just use Matplotlib's Hist Function from the start.
那还是用 Matplotlib 的 hist 函数来绘制吧